(Raj:)But when I said,
"Emily was cool with it.
(Raj:)Emily's the best. Why can't you
be more like Emily?.....
...those feelings
became less mixed.
(Leonard:)Women. Who knows what'll set 'em off?
(Raj:)At least now I can focus all
my energies on just one girl.
(Howard:)I hope I get to meet her
as soon as possible.
(Raj:)Why the rush?
She isn't going anywhere.
(Howard:)She is. But I like that attitude.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, is anybody interested
in my old string theory books?
(Raj:)You're really going to do this?
(Sheldon:)I am. Yeah, Penny pointed out
(Sheldon:)that what I'm going through
is essentially a breakup.
(Sheldon:)And according
to Cosmopolitan magazine,
(Sheldon:)one of the most effective
techniques for moving on
(Sheldon:)is to get rid of all reminders
of the relationship.
(Howard:)-You're reading Cosmo?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)As it turns out, there's an article
(Sheldon:)on how to get over a breakup
in literally every issue.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, it suggests
that I set these on fire,